http://www.jkj.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Please review this information carefully.
Our privacy policy.
Important information for your use of our website.
Johnson, Kendall & Johnson, Inc. has adopted the following privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of all information we use when providing our services.
Johnson, Kendall & Johnson, Inc collects information about our customers from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as employee names, address, and date of birth.
Information about our clients’ transactions with us, such as claims and payment history.
Information we receive from insurance companies, such as large claim or medical management information.
We do not share information about our customers or former customers with non-affiliated third parties other than as permitted or required by law, and to provide those services usual and customary to independent insurance agents. Such services include but are not limited to insurance underwriting, marketing the renewal, rating, placement, and providing quotes for insurance.
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your information. These safeguards include but are not limited to the following:
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about our clients and former clients to those employees who need to know that information in order to assist in providing services or products to the customer.
We will punish any employees who impermissibly share client information.
We use a secure Internet and e-mail provider to protect the confidentiality of electronic communications.
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
Johnson, Kendall & Johnson, Inc. 109 Pheasant Run Newtown, PA 18940 215.968.4741 www.jkj.com
LEGAL
Copyright
Except as otherwise noted, the text and graphics provided on JKJ’s website are copyrighted by Johnson, Kendall & Johnson, Inc (JKJ). JKJ does, however, permit visitors to make a single copy of information published on JKJ’s website for their personal, non-commercial use or use within the organization that employs them. JKJ’s name, logos, and trademarks may not be otherwise used by the visitors in any manner without the prior written consent of JKJ.
Disclaimer
The information published on JKJ’s website is provided without charge as a convenience to visitors, to be used for informational purposes only. Although JKJ has made reasonable efforts to provide accurate information, there may be inadvertent technical or factual inaccuracies and typographical errors. JKJ does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the information, text, graphics, links, or other items contained on or accessed through JKJ’s website, and JKJ expressly disclaims liability for errors or omissions in these materials. JKJ reserves the right to make changes and corrections at any time, without notice.
THE INFORMATION PROVIDED ON JKJ’S WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE.” JKJ MAKES NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS WEBSITE.
JKJ assumes no responsibility for and expressly disclaims all liability for errors or omissions in, and use or interpretation by others of, any information presented here or contained on any linked sites, or on any other site accessed by or through JKJ’s website, or any site from which any person may have accessed JKJ’s website.
Visitors to JKJ’s website assume all responsibility and risk for the use of JKJ’s website. JKJ expressly disclaims all liability for the use or interpretation by others of information contained in this website. Decisions based on information contained in JKJ’s website are the sole responsibility of the visitor, and in exchange for using JKJ’s website the visitor agrees to hold JKJ harmless against any claims for damages arising from any decisions that the visitor makes based on such information.
By providing any information (such as feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, plans, or ideas) to JKJ, the visitor agrees that all such information shall be non-confidential and that JKJ shall have unlimited rights to use (or not use), distribute (or not distribute), reproduce (or not reproduce), and disclose (or not disclose) such information worldwide as JKJ deems appropriate, without compensation or acknowledgment of its source. JKJ’s rights of ownership in such information shall extend to, and JKJ shall be free to use, any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in information a visitor provides JKJ through JKJ’s website, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products or services incorporating or otherwise based on such information.
JKJ DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS AND ENDORSEMENTS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH REGARD TO INFORMATION ACCESSED FROM OR VIA JKJ’S WEBSITE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ALL EXPRESS AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING THE WARRANTY OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS. IN NO EVENT SHALL JKJ BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES OF WHATSOEVER KIND RESULTING FROM WHATEVER CAUSE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF PROFITS, OR LOSS OF DATA, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER THEORIES OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR STRICT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE INFORMATION ON, OR ACCESSED THROUGH, JKJ’S WEBSITE.
JKJ does not assume any liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of the information disclosed at or accessed through JKJ’s website. Reference in JKJ’s website to any products, services, processes, hypertext links, or other information, by trade name, trade mark, manufacturer, supplier, or otherwise does not necessarily constitute or imply JKJ’s endorsement, sponsorship, or
The next step is easy, call 800-343-0107
Or, Contact Us
About Johnson, Kendall & Johnson The Johnson, Kendall & Johnson family of companies, for over 60 years, has grown to be one of the premier insurance brokerage firms in the United States.
We’re focused on providing value-added and unique solutions with the most creative talent in the industry. Our associates work with our clients to address their unique issues and needs with service-oriented, value-driven and affordable risk management and insurance solutions, helping them to achieve their goals.
Website Accessibility
Our Partners
Our Core Values
Client-Focused
Commitment
Development
Professionalism
Connect with Us 109 Pheasant Run, Newtown, PA 18940
© 2020 Johnson, Kendall & Johnson.
All rights reserved.
ContactPowered by Forge3 ActiveAgency.
